Nathan Roberts

Résumé

Introduction

I'm Nathan Roberts, a product designer focusing on a human-centered design approach with a curiosity for technical details and a passion for growth. My best work is done in collaboration with others.

Since graduating college in 2006, I've been building digital experiences small and large. I launched and managed a small e-commerce business, then joined Oakley as an Interaction Designer. Later, I led the Interaction Design team for Oakley's digital experiences. Now I lead a product design team at Experian building the future of finance.

Contact

Email: nathan@nathanroberts.com

Web: http://nathanroberts.com

Phone: (309) 472-0156

Education

B.A., Communications
Bradley University
2006

Skills

Human-centered design with a focus on learning and iteration, front-end development (HTML, CSS/SCSS and JavaScript), code collaboration (Git/GitHub), some basic experience in Xcode and Android Studio.

Employment History

Experian, Product Design Lead (2017–present)

Collaborating with product teams to conduct user research, design prototypes, test them with clients and iterate based on learnings.

Oakley, Interaction Design Lead (2015 – 2016)

Designed and built e-commerce and marketing experiences for Oakley.com. Designed native mobile apps like Radar Pace, Surf Report and Mad Science.

Oakley, Interaction Designer (2013 – 2014)

Designed e-commerce flows, shopping experiences and marketing pages. Built and maintained a platform for non-commerce experiences with Craft CMS, Amazon S3 and MediaTemple.

Uftring Marketing Group, Designer (2012-2013)

Managed 5+ auto dealership websites, designed and coded marketing-driven landing pages, designed social media campaigns for sales events.

Haberfeld, Consultant (2010-2011)

Evaluated client application of customer acquisition and growth strategies, reported findings on field research to improve training and increase sales.

V Gallery, Designer and Developer (2008–2010)

Designed, coded, launched and managed a

Magento-based e-commerce business selling

<\$100K/yr of digital and physical products.